

□ (+61) 403280788 | **S**terryzhuo25@gmail.com | **©** terryyz | **th** terry-zhuo

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, machine reading comprehension and language model. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience _____

Monash Univeristy

Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY REZA HAFFARI

May. 2020 - Present

- Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a top conference paper in COLING 2020.

UNSW Sydney Sydney Sydney, Australia

CASUAL ACADEMIC

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation
- Teaching in ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals

Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY ARNE LAUCHT

Nov. 2019 - Sep. 2020

- · Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- Strongly recommended by Michael Wang.

Project

Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

CONTRIBUTOR, COLLABORATOR

May. 2020 - Present

- Star: 2.0k
- Fork: 408
- · Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

Sphinx Markdown Builder

Github

May. 2020 - Present

Contributor
• Star: 79

- · Fork: 28
- Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

Education

UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)

Sydney, Australia

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 88.2, Top 2% in Faculty of Engineering

Extracurricular Activity _____

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

Power Engineer

- Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.
- Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

ELSOC UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

Oct. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

Publication

COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering

COLING 2020

FARHAD MOGHIMIFAR, LIZHEN QU, YUE ZHUO, MAHSA BAKTASHMOTLAGH AND GHOLAMREZA HAFFARI

Honors & Awards

2019 Highly Commended Undergraduate, Dean's Honours List | UNSW Engineering
 2019 Taste of Research Winner, Taste of Research Scholarships | UNSW Engineering

Sydney, Australia Sydney, Australia

Service_____

2020 Volunteer (Zoom Host), WiNLP 2020

Seattle, WA